<resources>
    <string name="app_name">31 Days Project</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1\nMario</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2\nLuigi</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3\nPeach</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4\nBowser</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5\nYoshi</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6\nDonkey Kong</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7\nLink</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8\nZelda</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9\nSheik</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10\nGanondorf</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11\nSamus</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12\nKirby</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13\nFox</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14\nFalco</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15\nPikachu</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16\nJigglypuff</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17\nCaptain Falcon</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18\nNess</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19\nIce Climbers</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20\nMarth</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21\nMr. Game &amp; Watch</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22\nDiddy Kong</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23\nToon Link</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24\nZero Suit Samus</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25\nMeta Knight</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26\nKing Dedede</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27\nWolf</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28\nPokémon Trainer</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29\nLucario</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30\nLucas</string>

    <string name="text1">Mario - The iconic plumber known for rescuing Princess Peach in the Mushroom Kingdom.</string>
    <string name="text2">Luigi - Mario\'s younger brother, often joining him on adventures.</string>
    <string name="text3">Princess Peach - The kind-hearted ruler of the Mushroom Kingdom often kidnapped by Bowser.</string>
    <string name="text4">Bowser - The arch-nemesis of Mario, a powerful, fire-breathing turtle-like creature aiming to conquer the Mushroom Kingdom.</string>
    <string name="text5">Yoshi - A friendly dinosaur and Mario\'s loyal companion, known for eating enemies and flutter jumping.</string>
    <string name="text6">Donkey Kong - A powerful yet good-natured ape often seen battling Mario.</string>
    <string name="text7">Link - The courageous hero from The Legend of Zelda series, often tasked with rescuing Princess Zelda.</string>
    <string name="text8">Zelda - The wise and resourceful princess from The Legend of Zelda series.</string>
    <string name="text9">Sheik - Zelda\'s alter ego, a skilled warrior in The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time.</string>
    <string name="text10">Ganondorf - The primary antagonist in The Legend of Zelda series, seeking power and dominion.</string>
    <string name="text11">Samus - A bounty hunter in a powered exoskeleton suit known from the Metroid series.</string>
    <string name="text12">Kirby - A cute but powerful pink puffball known for inhaling enemies and copying their abilities.</string>
    <string name="text13">Fox - The leader of the Star Fox team, an ace pilot skilled in space combat.</string>
    <string name="text14">Falco - A skilled and cocky member of the Star Fox team, known for his rivalry with Fox.</string>
    <string name="text15">Pikachu - The iconic electric-type Pokémon known for its lightning abilities.</string>
    <string name="text16">Jigglypuff - A singing Pokémon that lulls opponents to sleep with its melodies.</string>
    <string name="text17">Captain Falcon - A bounty hunter and skilled racer, famous for his powerful Falcon Punch move in the F-Zero series.</string>
    <string name="text18">Ness - A young psychic boy from the EarthBound series with psychic powers.</string>
    <string name="text19">Ice Climbers - A duo of characters, Popo and Nana, working together to climb icy mountains.</string>
    <string name="text20">Marth - A prince from the Fire Emblem series, known for his swordsmanship and honor.</string>
    <string name="text21">Mr. Game &amp; Watch - A flat 2D character with various abilities from the Game &amp; Watch series.</string>
    <string name="text22">Diddy Kong - Donkey Kong\'s nimble and quick-witted nephew, often joining him on adventures.</string>
    <string name="text23">Toon Link - The cartoonish version of Link from The Legend of Zelda series.</string>
    <string name="text24">Zero Suit Samus - Samus without her powered suit, showcasing her agility and speed.</string>
    <string name="text25">Meta Knight - A mysterious and powerful swordsman from the Kirby series.</string>
    <string name="text26">King Dedede - A penguin-like character from the Kirby series, often seen as both a rival and friend of Kirby.</string>
    <string name="text27">Wolf - A rival of Fox and a skilled pilot from the Star Fox series.</string>
    <string name="text28">Pokémon Trainer - A character who commands Squirtle, Ivysaur, and Charizard in battle.</string>
    <string name="text29">Lucario - A powerful Aura Pokémon known for its martial arts abilities.</string>
    <string name="text30">Lucas - A character from the Mother/EarthBound series known for his PSI abilities and kind-hearted nature.</string>
</resources>

